{
    "id": "eb8018166d6a4dd2a24f59426c51fe7a",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The train …………….. at",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about future events that are part of a timetable. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrives",
                "will arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "490e6af041354fdaaf2a5aac63ac1971"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will meet you when he ………………… back.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the simple future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "comes",
                "will come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6f76ee67bfa4352b79bf363e763b8f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I got home, my dog ………………. at the gate waiting for me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sits",
                "sat",
                "was sitting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3397b29d8b1a49a786678c4d725f0cbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. Gupta this evening.",
            "description": "If the arrangement already exists, we use the present continuous tense to talk about future. ",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "will visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8766fb95ccee491cb0c5abfd4d872e12"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at the sky. It ………………….. to rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is going",
                "goes",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6b30f67c28f492296a2e373c1dae57f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train ………………… before we reach the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive",
                "will have arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af63b73e91c54fc0824630b30174dd8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Perhaps we ………………. Singapore next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "will visit",
                "are visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11ca7bf57c3c41209f93be417ec6fd5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The next term ………………. on Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "begins",
                "will begin"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "212c950a06134ed6b606e30cbb557cfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Oh dear! I …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will die",
                "am dying",
                "die"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7b9c604d5ea444fb137fe6c0c80232c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m sure she ……………….. the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "will get",
                "would get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d54eb6821d84e1d8cdbe4f0d6c76acd"
        }
    ]
}